Guide to the Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Papers AIA.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V. Commercial Recordings, 1916-1992, undated; 28.5 Linear Feet in 9 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and 19 packing boxes
  - 45 rpm Recordings, 1916-1992; 1958-1988; 7.85 Linear Feet in 13 small LP boxes
    - Side A: Sheridan, J.J., "Danny Boy" Side B: Sheridan, J.J., "O'Carolan's Concerto", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 23)
    - Side A: Carton, Mickey, "Stack of Barley" and "Kerry Mills Barn Dance" Side B: Carton, Mickey, "Keel Row" and "Green Grows The Rushes O", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 24)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "Abbeyshrule" Side B: Shine, Brendan, "Ballinasloe Fair", 1974 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 25)
    - Side A: Winch, Terry, "When New York Was Irish" Side B: O'Farrell, Frank, "Here In America", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 26)
    - Side A: Patterson, Frank, "Farewell My Derry Love" Side B: Patterson, Frank, "Castle Of Dromore", 1989 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 27)
    - Side A: Barley Corn, "Men Behind The Wire" Side B: Barley Corn, "Freedom Walk", 1971 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 28)
    - Side A: Greehy, Anne, "The Irish Patrol" Side B: Greehy, Anne, "Wrap The Green Flag Round Me", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 29)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Two Rivers" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "The Whistling Gypsy", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 30)
    - Side A: Makem & Clancy, "Morning Glory" Side B: Makem & Clancy, "Cruisin Lan", 1979 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 31)
    - Side A: Prunty, John, "The Greenfields of Longford" Side B: Prunty, John, "The Old Woman From Wexford", 1985 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 32)
    - Side A: Allen, Denis, "Limerick You're A Lady" Side B: Allen, Denis, "For Jenny", 1979 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 33)
    - Side A: Grace, Brendan, "The Combine Harvester" Side B: Grace, Brendan, "Bottler At The Circus", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 34)
    - Side A: Coleman, Michael, "The Boys At The Lough" Side B: Coleman, Michael, "The Liverpool - O'Neill's", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 35)
    - Side A: Na Brollaigh, "H Block" Side B: Na Brollaigh, "Freedom Sons", 1979 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 36)
    - Side A: Doyle, Danny, "The Blarney Roses" Side B: Doyle, Danny, "The Town Of Castle D'Oliver", 1982 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 37)
    - Side A: Supple, Art, "The Boys Of Kilmichael" Side B: Supple, Art, "Big Chief Buffalo Nickel", 1969 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 38)
    - Side A: Byrne, Mike, "Galway Girl" Side B: Byrne, Mike, "The Boys Won't Leave The Girls Alone", 1985 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 39)
    - Side A: Bishop & Seeger, "Run Children Run" Side B: Bishop & Seeger, "My Brother John", 1987 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 40)
    - Side A: McEvoy, Johnny, "Time And Time Again" Side B: McEvoy, Johnny, "A Hedgehog Song", 1968 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 41)
    - Side A: McEvoy, Johnny, "My Mary Of The Curling Hair" Side B: McEvoy, Johnny, "Hickory Wind", 1969 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 42)
    - Side A: Daly, Pat, "The Boys of Barna Straide" Side B: Daly, Pat, "Three Leaf Shamrock, I Adore Thee", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 43)
    - Side A: Harrington, Al, "I Want A Daddy For Christmas" Side B: Harrington, Al, "Dream Away", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 44)
    - Side A: Dolan, Joe, "Two of A Kind", "I've Got Five Dollars and it's Saturday Night", "I'll Sit on Your Doorstep" Side B: Dolan, Joe, "Minutes to Midnight" and "The Jolly Tinker", 1966 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 45)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Jerry, "Tick Tock Clock" Side B: O'Brien, Jerry, "Stranger In My Heart", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 46)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Jerry, "The Tower That Leans On The Sky" Side B: O'Brien, Jerry, "The Tower That Leans On The Sky", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 47)
    - Side A: Black, Mary, "As I Leave Behind Neidin" Side B: Black, Mary, "Ellis Island", 1986 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 48)
    - Side A: McAnally, Ray, "The Rebel" and "Renunciation" Side B: McAnally, Ray, "The Fool" and "The Proclamation", 1966 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 49)
    - Side A: McCann, Jim, "Grace" Side B: McCann, Jim, "Spancil Hill", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 50)
    - Side A: Big Tom & The Mainliners, "The G.N.R. Steam Train" Side B: Big Tom & The Mainliners, "Mainliners Magic Mix", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 51)
    - Side A: McGee, Charlie, "Come Home To Stay" and "Dreamer From Ireland" Side B: McGee, Charlie, "Lovely Annascaul" and "Skibereen", 1960 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 52)
    - Side A: Bowyer, Brendan, "The Rapparee" Side B: Bowyer, Brendan, "Whistlin' Phil McHugh", 1967 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 53)
    - Side A: Glynn, Jack, "Welcome To Limerick" Side B: Glynn Jack, "By Shannonside", 1967 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 54)
    - Side A: Harris, Rolf, "I Love My Love" Side B: Harris, Rolf, "Two Little Boys", 1969 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 55)
    - Side A: Shamrocks for Dystrophy, "Public Service Radio Announcements" Side B: Shamrocks for Dystrophy, "Public Service Radio Announcements", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 56)
    - Side A: Gerry & The Ohios, "Fishing For The Shoal" Side B: Gerry & The Ohios, "Bobby (Tribute to R.F.K.)", 1968 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 57)
    - Side A: Kelly, Johnny, "Black Velvet Band" Side B: Kelly, Johnny, "The Nightingale", 1967 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 58)
    - Side A: Gerry & The Ohios, "Fishing For The Shoal" Side B: Gerry & The Ohios, "Bobby (Tribute to R.F.K.)", 1968 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 59)
    - Side A: Gill, Earl, "Sunset" Side B: Gill, Earl, "If I Could Choose", 1967 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 60)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry, "Good-bye Comes Hard For Me" and "Picture Of Your Mother" Side B: Cunningham, Larry, "A Kingdom I Call Home" and "I Guess I Had Too Much To Dream", 1973 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 61)
    - Side A: The Ludlows, "Johnny Lad" Side B: The Ludlows, "Pack Up Your Sorrows", 1966 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 62)
    - Side A: Vaughan, Martin, "Claddagh Ring" Side B: The Tulla Ceili Band, "The Boys of Ballinahinch", 1970 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 63)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "Talking Love" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "The Blizzard", 1967 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 64)
    - Side A: Owens, Jesse, "Mary Of The Wild Moor" Side B: Owens, Jesse, "The Irish Soldier", 1967 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 1)
    - Side A: Murphy, Pat, "Barry McGuigan" and "The Irish Cyclone" Side B: Murphy, Pat, "Danny Boy", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 2)
    - Side A: Patterson, Frank, "Farewell My Derry Love" Side B: Patterson, Frank, "Castle Of Dromore", 1989 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 3)
    - Side A: Daly, Pat, "The Boys of Barna Straide" Side B: Daly, Pat, "Three Leaf Shamrock, I Adore Thee", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 4)
    - Side A: Tara, "State Music" Side B: Tara, "May Morning Dew", 1984 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 5)
    - Side A: Logan, Al, "Belfast" Side B: Logan, Al, "Four Roads to Glenamady", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 6)
    - Side A: The Light Blues, "Heffo's Heroes" Side B: The Light Blues, "The Dubs Are Back", 1974 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 7)
    - Side A: Kelly, Frank, "Charlie Stepped In" Side B: Kelly, Frank, "Christmas Countdown", 1980 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 8)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "The Taker" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "Sunday Morning Coming Down", 1971 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 9)
    - Side A: Big Tom and the Mainliners, "Please Mama Please" Side B: Big Tom and the Mainliners, "The Old Rustic Bridge", 1968 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 10)
    - Side A: Carey, Dan, "Lady Liberty" Side B: Carey, Dan, "Lady Liberty (Long Version)", 1985 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 11)
    - Side A: Bishop & Seeger, "Run Children Run" Side B: Bishop & Seeger, "My Brother John", 1987 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 12)
    - Side A: Curran, Frankie, "Something To Sing About" Side B: Curran, Frankie, "Ringsend Rose", 1985 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 13)
    - Side A: Curran, Frankie, "Something To Sing About" Side B: Curran, Frankie, "Ringsend Rose", 1985 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 14)
    - Side A: O'Gill, Darby, "Poor Poor Farmer" Side B: O'Gill, Darby, "Hairy Eggs and Bacon", 1971 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 15)
    - Side A: O'Se, Sean, "Farewell to Galway" Side B: O'Se, Sean, "Bob Riddley", 1973 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 16)
    - Side A: Coll, Brian, "Asthoreen Bawn" Side B: Coll, Brian, "I'll Be Glad To Help You Out", 1969 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 17)
    - Side A: The Clancy Brothers, "Freedom Sons" Side B: The Clancy Brothers, "O'Donnell Abu", 1966 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 18)
    - Side A: The Witnesses Showband, "Johnny McEldoo" Side B: The Witnesses Showband, "The Jarvey Was A Leprechaun", 1966 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 19)
    - Side A: Gunner, Jim, "Men of Ireland's 32" Side B: Gunner, Jim, "The West's Awake", 1966 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 20)
    - Side A: Brady, Willie, "Where Are You Going And How Are You Doing?" Side B: Brady, Willie, "Down In The Cane Brake", 1968 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 21)
    - Side A: Gallagher, Bridie, "Henry Joy" Side B: Gallagher, Bridie, "The Glen of Aherlow", 1967 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 22)
    - 1966 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 23)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "The Johnny Thompson Song" and "Flower Of Macroom" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "Danny Boy" and "Black and Tan Gun", 1966 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 24)
    - Side A: Gallagher, Bridie, "If I Were A Blackbird" Side B: Gallagher, Bridie, "Moon Behind The Hill", 1959 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 25)
    - Side A: The Reapers, "Banks Of The Ohio" Side B: The Reapers, "Galway Bay", 1967 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 26)
    - Side A: Quinn, John, "Holyoke In Green" Side B: Quinn, John, "Queen of the Green", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 27)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "Christmas Polka" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "She's Mine", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 28)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "Where The 3 Counties Meet" Side B: Shine, Brendan, "Bright City Lights", 1973 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 29)
    - Side A: McEvoy, Johnny, "Rose of Moray" and "James Connelly" Side B: McEvoy, Johnny, "Nora", "Teardrop On A Rose", and "Leitrim Queen", 1974 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 30)
    - Side A: Bishop & Seeger, "Run Children Run" Side B: Bishop & Seeger, "My Brother John", 1987 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 31)
    - Side A: Foster & Allen, "Ben Bulben" Side B: Foster & Allen, "The Emmigrant", 1980 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 32)
    - Side A: Rotton Spuds, "Emerald Green" Side B: Rotton Spuds, "Spinning Wheel", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 33)
    - Side A: O'Se, Sean, "Priosun Chluain Meala" Side B: O'Se, Sean, "The Valley Of Knockanure" (empty sleeve), 1968 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 34)
    - Side A: Murphy, John, "The Lark" Side B: Murphy, John, "Galway Girl", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 35)
    - Side A: Big Tom and the Travellers, "The Streets of Dublin City" Side B: Big Tom and the Travellers, "5,000 Miles from Sligo", 1981 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 36)
    - Side A: Doherty, Robert, "Drop Off In Ballyporeen" Side B: Doherty, Robert, "Slievenamon", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 37)
    - Side A: The All Star Ceilidhe Band, "The Girl I Left Behind Me & The Rakes of Mallow Polkas" and "Fire on the Mountain & The Cook in the Kitchen Jigs" Side B: The All Star Ceilidhe Band, "When The Kettle Boils Over & The Leg of the Duck Jigs" and "The Blackberry Blossom & Bonnie Kate Reels", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 38)
    - Side A: Reilly, Tommy, "The Bard of Armagh" and "That's How I Spell I-R-E-L-A-N-D" Side B: Reilly, Tommy, "Bendemeer's Stream" and "You're Irish and You're Beautiful", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 39)
    - Side A: Cronin, Paddy, "Galway Reel", "The Woman of The House Reel", "The Butcher's March", and "Old Man Dillon Jigs" Side B: Cronin, Paddy, "Paddy Finley's Reel", "The Red Haired Lass Reel", "The Clare Reel", "The Maid in the Cherry Tree Reel", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 40)
    - Side A: Grabeau, Bob, "If Pearse Came Back" Side B: McConville, Tom, "If Pearse Came Back", 1978 (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 41)
    - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "White Christmas" Side B: Crosby, Bing, "God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 42)
    - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "My Girl's An Irish Girl" Side B: Crosby, Bing, "Galway Bay", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 43)
    - Side A: Crosby, Bing, "Christmas In Killarney" Side B: Crosby, Bing, "It's Beginning To Look Like Christmas", undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 44)
    - Side A: Margo & Co., "Shamrock From Glenore" and "Cliffs Of Dooneen" Side B: Margo & Co., "Bonnie Scotland" and "Road & The Miles To Dundee" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 45)
    - Side A: Big Tom and the Travellers, "The Streets of Dublin City" Side B: Big Tom and the Travellers, "5,000 Miles from Sligo" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 46)
    - Side A: MacNally, John, "Kathleen Mavourneen" and "The Star of the County Down" Side B: MacNally, John, "Macushla" and "The Old House" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 47)
    - Side A: The Gallowglass Ceili Band, "Hornpipe" and "Irish March" Side B: The Gallowglass Ceili Band, "Military Two-Step" and "Set Dance" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 48)
    - Side A: O'Duffy, Michael, "The Kerry Dance" and "Kitty Magee" Side B: O'Duffy, Michael, "Little Town In Old County Down" and "Because I Love You So (Machree)" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 49)
    - Side A: Ruane, Jack, "The River Moy" Side B: Ruane, Jack, "What About The Last Time" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 50)
    - Tara (empty sleeve), undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 51)
    - Side A: Big Tom and the Travellers, "Four Country Roads" Side B: Big Tom and the Travellers, "My Rose of the Mountain" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 52)
    - Side A: O'Se, Sean, "Priosun Chluain Meala" Side B: O'Se, Sean, "The Valley Of Knockanure" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 53)
    - Kingston, Noel, "Love Thee Dearest", "The Village That Nobody Knows", "Because I Love You So Machree", and "Bless This House" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 85, Sound disc--vinyl 54)
    - Home Sweet Home Vocal Quartette, "When Yankee Doodle Sails," "Upon the Good Ship", undated
- Series VI. Irish Memories Radio Program Recordings, 1944-1997; 1.75 Linear Feet; 4.1 Linear Feet in 4 media boxes, 1 record carton, and 1 flat box
  This series consists of audio recordings of the Irish Memories radio program. The recordings date from 1944 to 1997 and consist of musical selections, news, advertisements, interviews, and other segments.
  - Fidelipac Recordings, undated
    - Cartridge 170: Budweiser 1/13: 60, undated (Box 37, Item 170, Box 44)
    - Cartridge 171: Budweiser 1/13: 60, undated (Box 37, Item 171, Box 44)
    - Cartridge 172: Bud #3, undated (Box 37, Item 172, Box 44)
    - Cartridge 173: Dorothy Hayden's "Irish Memories" Theme 1'35", undated (Box 37, Item 173, Box 44)
    - Cartridge 174: D. Hayden Woodside Steakhouse: 60, undated (Box 37, Item 174, Box 44)
    - Cartridge 175: Mary Kate, undated (Box 37, Item 175, Box 44)
  - Cassette Tapes, 1944-1997
    - Cassette 106: Aer Lingus:60 50th Anniversary, undated (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 106)
    - Cassette 107: Irish Tourist Board "$399 Fare", undated (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 107)
    - Cassette 108: Allied Bank (2X): 70, undated (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 108)
    - Cassette 109: Morbert 6-6, Hennessy, Kevin O'Connor, Mar 1982 (Box 86, Cassette 109)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      This cassette is blank.
    - Cassette 110: Morbert, Kevin O'Connor, Elmer Ford, 1982-1983 (Box 86, Cassette 110, Box 42)
    - Cassette 111: "Guy LeBow at Large", re: Grand Marshall, 10 Feb 1989 (Box 86, Cassette 111, Box 42)
    - Cassette 125: Kevin O'Connor, 1983 (Box 86, Cassette 125, Box 43)
    - Cassette 130: Irish Forum with John Dearks, undated (Box 86, Cassette 130, Box 43)
    - Cassette 132: Teddy Gleason, undated (Box 42, Box 86, Cassette 132)
    - Cassette 134: Aer Lingus Inflight Program - Irish Festival (from Milwaukee), Mar 1997 (Box 42, Box 86, Cassette 134)
    - Cassette 138: David Andrews, undated (Box 42, Box 86, Cassette 138)
    - Cassette 141: Untitled, undated (Box 42, Box 86, Cassette 141)
    - Cassette 143: Kevin O'Connor, Mar 1983 (Box 86, Cassette 143, Box 42)
    - Cassette 148: Jack Irwin, Dec 1989 (Box 86, Cassette 148, Box 42)
    - Cassette 150: Bernadette Devlin, McAleskey, Kevin O'Connor, Dec 1981 (Box 86, Cassette 150, Box 42)
    - Cassette 152: Kevin O'Connor, Father Francis MacNamara, 1981 (Box 86, Cassette 152, Box 42)
    - Cassette 164: Monica Burke, LAOH President, undated (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 164)
    - Cassette 165: Timmy O'Sullivan, Kevin O'Connor, 1983 (Box 86, Cassette 165, Box 43)
    - Cassette 166: O'Dwyer, undated (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 166)
    - Cassette 167: Kevin O'Connor, Dorothy Interviews Rockaway Festival, 1982 (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 167)
    - Cassette 168: Allied Irish Bank, New Years '44, Falker Slattery, 1944 (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 168)
    - Cassette 169: Sean O'Sheicain, Con Murphy - Paddy Grimes, undated (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 169)
    - Cassette 213: Mike Mugehy / Norbert Hennessy, undated (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 213)
    - Cassette 214: Dorothy Hayden's "Irish Memories" - Sheila DeValera, Apr 28, 1989 (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 214)
    - Cassette 215: Kevin O'Connor / Minester Peter Barry, 1983 (Box 86, Cassette 215, Box 43)
    - Cassette 216: Meeting Press, Mar 15, 1983 (Box 86, Cassette 216, Box 43)
    - Cassette 217: Broadcast of Jan 2, 1992 (Joan Hamburg Around NY) (Box 86, Cassette 217, Box 43)
    - Cassette 218: Sean MacBride / W. O'Donnel, Jan 2, 1983 (Box 86, Cassette 218, Box 43)
    - Cassette 219: Broadcast of Jan 2, 1992 (Box 86, Item 219, Box 43)
    - Cassette 220: "Her Excellency Mary Robinson, President of Ireland, Addresses the Columbia University Irish Studies Seminar; Introduction by Thomas F. Heffernan, May 19, 1993 (Box 86, Cassette 220, Box 43)
    - Cassette 221: Pat Finucane, May 1984 (Box 86, Cassette 221, Box 43)
    - Cassette 222: "A Personal Serenade to Grand Marshall Dorothy Hayden Cudahy by Phyllis Tarter, undated (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 222)
    - Cassette 223: Dorothy Hayden's "Irish Memories" - Guest Mayor Ed Koch, Mar 10, 1989 (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 223)
    - Cassette 224: Radio Free Eireann - "The Great Hunger", Oct 16, 1996 (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 224)
    - Cassette 225: "Irish Memories" Guest Peter King, Nov 18, 1988 (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 225)
    - Cassette 226: Dorothy Hayden Show - T. Gleason, undated (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 226)
    - Cassette 227: William D. Griffin interviewed on WNYC's "New York Beat" re: The Book of Irish Americans, circa 1991 (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 227)
    - Cassette 228: John Cudahy, Gerry Adams, undated (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 228)
    - Cassette 229: Dorothy Hayden Show - H. Goldin, Jan 20, 1989 (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 229)
    - Cassette 230: Rev. Jerry Connoly, Tom Dayle, Dec 2, 1984 (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 230)
    - Cassette 231: Con Howard, Jul 1, 1982 (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 231)
    - Cassette 232: Kevin O'Connor, 1982-1985 (Box 43, Box 86, Cassette 232)
  - Compact Discs, undated
    - Audio Disc 1001, Tracks 1-4, undated (Box 54, Cd 1001)
    - Audio Disc 1002, Tracks 1-6/6, undated (Box 54, Cd 1002)
    - Audio Disc 1003, Tracks 1-8/8, undated (Box 54, Cd 1003)
    - Audio Disc 1004, Tracks 1/1, undated (Box 54, Cd 1004)
    - Audio Disc 1005, Tracks 1-7/7, undated (Box 54, Cd 1005)
    - Audio Disc 1007, Tracks 1-5/5, undated (Box 54, Cd 1007)
    - Audio Disc 1009, Tracks 1-9/9, undated (Box 54, Cd 1009)
    - Audio Disc 1011, Tracks 1-2/2, undated (Box 54, Cd 1011)
    - Audio Disc 1013, Tracks 1/1, undated (Box 54, Cd 1013)
    - Audio Disc 1015, Tracks 1-8, undated (Box 54, Cd 1015)
    - Audio Disc 1018, Tracks 1-5/5, undated (Box 54, Cd 1018)
    - Audio Disc 1020, Tracks 1-5, undated (Box 54, Cd 1020)
    - Audio Disc 1021, Tracks 1-7/7, undated (Box 54, Cd 1021)
    - Audio Disc 1022, Tracks 1-12/12, undated (Box 54, Cd 1022)
    - Audio Disc 1023, Tracks 1-13, undated (Box 54, Cd 1023)
    - Audio Disc 1024, Tracks 1-7/7, undated (Box 54, Cd 1024)
    - Audio Disc 1025, Tracks 1-8/8, undated (Box 54, Cd 1025)
    - Audio Disc 1026, Tracks 1-8/8, undated (Box 54, Cd 1026)
    - Audio Disc 1027, Tracks 1-15/15, undated (Box 54, Cd 1027)
    - Audio Disc 1028, Tracks 1-5/5, undated (Box 54, Cd 1028)
    - Audio Disc 1029, undated (Box 54, Cd 1029)
    - Audio Disc 1030, undated (Box 54, Cd 1030)
    - Data Disc 1031, undated (Box 54, Cd 1031)
  - Reel-to-Reel Tapes, 1968-1989
    - Reel 101, undated (Box 36, Box 42)
    - Reel 102: Unidentified, undated (Box 36, Reel 102, Box 42)
    - Reel 103: "Phil Coultor" Spot: 60, undated (Box 36, Reel 103, Box 42)
    - Reel 104: Budweiser Beer: Tape BB 88-66 "Irish 1988 Revised", Aug 10, 1988 (Box 42, Box 36, Reel 104)
    - Reel 105: Pan Am: PN-82-110 "Experience/Open": 60 sec., 1982 (Box 42, Box 36, Reel 105)
    - Reel 112, Apr 13, 1975 (Box 42, Box 36)
    - Reel 113: "Dawn Over the Hills of Ireland" By Dep/Comm. James J. O'Brien, 1968 (Box 42, Box 36, Reel 113)
    - Reel 114: Allied Irish Bank: 3 Spots, 60 sec., undated (Box 42, Box 36, Reel 114)
    - Reel 115: Irish International Airlines, Jul 15, 1969 (Box 44, Box 87, Reel 115)
    - Reel 116: (Dig. CD 1006, Track 1), undated (Box 44, Cd 1006, Track 1, Box 36, Reel 116)
    - Reel 117, undated (Box 36, Box 42)
    - Reel 118, undated (Box 42, Box 87)
    - Reel 119, undated (Box 42, Box 36)
    - Reel 120: Allied Bank: 8 Spots, Jun 1979 (Box 36, Reel 120, Box 42)
    - Reel 121: Radio City: Frank Patterson, "Great Night for the Irish", undated (Box 36, Reel 121, Box 42)
    - Reel 122: Fort Worth 5, undated (Box 42, Box 36, Reel 122)
    - Reel 123: Hidden Agenda "War Film": 60 (Dig. CD 1008, Track 14), undated (Box 36, Reel 123, Box 44, Cd 1008, Track 14)
    - Reel 124: Allied Irish Bank-2 Track/Stereo, undated (Box 42, Box 36, Reel 124)
    - Reel 126: Extracts from new Michael Coleman Album – 12 inch L.P. 7 1/2" per sec (Dig. CD 1010, Track 1), undated (Box 44, Cd 1010, Track 1, Box 36, Reel 126)
    - Reel 127, undated (Box 87, Box 44)
    - Reel 128: New York 3/16/1975, Mar 16, 1975 (Box 36, Reel 128, Box 42)
    - Reel 129: Greetings: Treasa Dawson plus end of Will Reagan Show (Dig. CD 1010, Track 3), undated (Box 44, Cd 1010, Track 3, Box 36, Reel 129)
    - Reel 131: News Special: Ronald Reagan in Ireland (Dig. CD 1012, Track 1), 1984 (Box 44, Cd 1012, Track 1, Box 36, Reel 131)
    - Reel 133: Interview: John Dearie (copy of Tape 130; Dig CD. 1012, Track 2), 1989 (Box 44, Cd 1012, Track 2, Box 36, Reel 133)
    - Reel 135: Commercials: Allied Irish Bank (Dig. CD 1014, Tracks 1-3), undated (Box 44, Cd 1014, Track 1-3, Box 36, Reel 135)
    - Reel 136: Music: Seamus O'Doherty, Josephine Patricia Smith and Marie Maxwell (Dig. CD 1014, Track 4), undated (Box 36, Reel 136, Box 44, Cd 1014, Track 4)
    - Reel 137: Easter 1916 Rising (Dig. CD 1014, Track 5), undated (Box 36, Reel 137, Box 44, Cd 1014, Track 5)
    - Reel 139: Greetings: Treasa Dawson (Dig. CD 1016, Track 1), undated (Box 36, Reel 139, Box 44, Cd 1016, Track 1)
    - Reel 140: Greetings: Treasa Dawson (Dig. CD 1016, Track 2), undated (Box 36, Reel 140, Box 44, Cd 1016, Track 2)
    - Reel 142: News: Eyewitness accounts from Northern Ireland (Dig. CD 1016, Track 3), undated (Box 36, Reel 142, Box 44, Cd 1016, Track 3)
    - Reel 144: Music, undated (Box 36, Reel 144, Box 42)
    - Reel 145: Unidentified, undated (Box 36, Reel 145, Box 42)
    - Reel 146: Music (Dig. CD 1017, Track 1), undated (Box 87, Reel 146, Box 44, Cd 1017, Track 1)